Guide to the Ray Lyman Wilbur, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0064A
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- 1940-1941, Series 25
  - Psychology (Box 253, Folder 3)
  - Public Relations (Box 253, Folder 4)
  - Publicity (Box 253, Folder 5)
  - Q (Box 253, Folder 6)
  - Quad (Box 253, Folder 7)
  - Questionnaires (Box 253, Folder 8)
  - Ra (Box 253, Folder 11)
  - Radio (Box 253, Folder 12)
  - Recommendation, Letters of (Box 253, Folder 13)
  - Refunder's Club (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - Registrar, September - February (Box 253, Folder 14)
  - Registrar, March - August (Box 253, Folder 15)
  - Religion, School of (Box 254, Folder 2)
  - Republican Program Committee (Box 254, Folder 3)
  - Requisitions - Travel Fund - Completed (Box 253, Folder 10)
  - Requisitions - Travel Fund Requests (Box 253, Folder 9)
  - Rhodes Scholarship Committee (Box 254, Folder 4)
  - Ro (Box 254, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 254, Folder 6)
  - Romanic Laguages (Box 254, Folder 7)
  - Sa (Box 254, Folder 8)
  - San Francisco (Box 254, Folder 9)
  - Sc (Box 254, Folder 10)
  - Se (Box 254, Folder 11)
  - Slavic Languages (Box 254, Folder 12)
  - Sm (Box 254, Folder 13)
  - Smith, Mrs. Alfred E. (Box 254, Folder 17)
  - Social Science Research Council (Box 254, Folder 15)
  - Social Sciences, School of (Box 254, Folder 14)
  - Sororities (Box 254, Folder 16)
  - Speech and Drama - English (Box 254, Folder 18)
  - St (Box 254, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Associates, September - November (Box 255, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Associates, December - February (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Associates, March - May (Box 255, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Associates, June - August (Box 255, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 255, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Fiftieth Anniversary (Box 238, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Fund, September - October (Box 238, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Fund, November - December (Box 238, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Fund, January - February (Box 238, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Fund, March - April (Box 238, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Fund, May - June (Box 238, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Fund, July - August (Box 238, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Fund (Box 255, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Illustrated Review (Box 256, Folder 3)
  - Stanford National Emergency Committee (Box 244, Folder 7)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 238, Folder 15)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 256, Folder 4)
  - Statistics (Box 238, Folder 16)
  - Statistics (Box 256, Folder 5)
  - Su (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - Su (Box 256, Folder 6)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 256, Folder 7)
  - T (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - T (Box 256, Folder 8)
  - Teacher Tenure (Box 239, Folder 6)
  - Trustees (Box 239, Folder 4)
  - Trustees (Box 256, Folder 9)
  - Tuition (Box 239, Folder 5)
  - Tuition (Box 256, Folder 10)
  - U - V (Box 239, Folder 7)
  - U - V (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - U. S. Naval Reserve (Box 257, Folder 4)
  - Unique (Box 257, Folder 2)
  - United States (Box 239, Folder 8)
  - United States (Box 257, Folder 3)
  - Wa (Box 239, Folder 9)
  - Wa (Box 257, Folder 5)
  - West Memorial Lecture Fund (Box 257, Folder 7)
  - West Memorial Lectures (Box 239, Folder 10)
  - Wh (Box 239, Folder 11)
  - Wh (Box 257, Folder 8)
  - Wittman, Joseph Van Buren (Box 257, Folder 9)
  - Wo (Box 239, Folder 12)
  - Wo (Box 257, Folder 10)
  - Women's Council (Box 239, Folder 13)
  - Women's Council (Box 257, Folder 11)
  - World Citizen's Association (Box 239, Folder 14)
  - X-Y-Z (Box 257, Folder 12)
  - XYZ (Box 240, Folder 2)
  - Y.M.C.A & Y.W.C.A (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - Y.M.C.A & Y.W.C.A (Box 257, Folder 13)
- 1941-1942, Series 26
  - A (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - Private - Alpha Delta Phi (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - Academic and Alumni Secretary (Box 258, Folder 3)
  - American, September - February (Box 258, Folder 4)
  - American, March - August (Box 258, Folder 5)
  - Annuity List (Box 258, Folder 6)
  - Anatomy (Box 259, Folder 1)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 259, Folder 2)
  - Assistants (Box 259, Folder 3)
  - Associated Students (Box 259, Folder 4)
  - Ba (Box 260, Folder 1)
  - Bacteriology (Box 260, Folder 2)
  - Be (Box 260, Folder 3)
  - Bequests (Box 260, Folder 4)
  - Bi (Box 260, Folder 5)
  - Big Game Tickets (Box 260, Folder 6)
  - Biology, School of (Box 260, Folder 7)
  - Biology - Mumford Pacific Island Research (Box 260, Folder 8)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 260, Folder 9)
  - Br (Box 260, Folder 10)
  - Bu (Box 260, Folder 11)
  - Budapest (Box 260, Folder 12)
  - Ca (Box 261, Folder 1)
  - California Colleges in China [folder is missing] (Box 261, Folder 2)
  - California, University of (Box 261, Folder 3)
  - Carnegie Endowment - International Peace (Box 261, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Corporation (Box 261, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 261, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Institute of Washington (Box 261, Folder 7)
  - Ch (Box 261, Folder 8)
  - Chaparral (Box 261, Folder 9)
  - Chemistry (Box 261, Folder 10)
  - Citizenship of Foreign Born - Questionnaires (Box 261, Folder 11)
  - Civil Aeronautics Authority (Box 261, Folder 12)
  - Classics (Box 261, Folder 13)
  - Co (Box 261, Folder 14)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System (Box 261, Folder 15)
  - Commencement (Box 261, Folder 16)
  - Commonwealth Fund (Box 261, Folder 17)
  - Conventions (Box 261, Folder 18)
  - Da (Box 262, Folder 1)
  - Dean of Men (Box 262, Folder 2)
  - Dean of Women (Box 262, Folder 3)
  - Deferment - Selective Service (Box 262, Folder 4)
  - Defense (Box 262, Folder 5)
  - Defense - Stanford National Emergency Committee (Box 262, Folder 6)
  - Defense - National Emergency Committee (Box 262, Folder 7)
  - Defense - Civilian Defense Council (Box 262, Folder 8)
  - Investigation by Government Agents (Box 262, Folder 9)
  - Defense - War Council (Box 262, Folder 10)
  - Dentistry, College of (Box 262, Folder 11)
  - Do (Box 262, Folder 12)
  - Dormitories (Box 262, Folder 13)
  - Economics (Box 263, Folder 1)
  - Education, School of (Box 263, Folder 2)
  - Education, School of, September - February (Box 263, Folder 3)
  - Education, School of, March, April, May (Box 263, Folder 4)
  - Education, School of, June, July, August (Box 263, Folder 5)
  - Education, Proposal for University Committee on Teacher Education (Box 263, Folder 6)
  - Education - 9th Service Command (1) (Box 263, Folder 7)
  - Education - 9th Service Command (2) (Box 263, Folder 8)
  - Electron Microscope (Box 263, Folder 9)
  - Engineering, Science and Management War Training Contracts, September - February (Box 264, Folder 1)
  - Engineering, Science and Management War Training Contracts, March - August (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - Engineering, Science and Management War Training Correspondence (Box 264, Folder 3)
  - Engineering, Science and Management War Training Literature (Box 264, Folder 4)
  - Engineering, Civil (Box 264, Folder 5)
  - Engineering, Electrical (Box 264, Folder 6)
  - Engineering, Guggenheim Lab. (Box 264, Folder 7)
  - Engineering, Mechanical (Box 264, Folder 8)
  - Engineering, Military Science and Tactics (Box 265, Folder 1)
  - Engineering, Mining (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - Engineering, School of (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - English (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - English - Dramatists' Alliance (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - E (Box 265, Folder 6)
  - Fa (Box 265, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Housing (Box 265, Folder 8)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 265, Folder 9)
  - Fellowships (Box 265, Folder 10)
  - Financial Vice-President, September, October, November (Box 265, Folder 11)
  - Financial Vice-President, December, January, February (Box 265, Folder 12)
  - Financial Vice-President, March, April, May (Box 265, Folder 13)
  - Financial Vice-President, June, July, August (Box 265, Folder 14)
  - Fo (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - Food Rsearch Institute (Box 266, Folder 2)
  - Fraternities (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Ga (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - General Education Board (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - Geology (Box 266, Folder 6)
  - Germanic Languages (Box 266, Folder 7)
  - Germanic Languages - Appointments, Leaves, Resignations (Box 266, Folder 8)
  - Gi (Box 266, Folder 9)
  - Gl (Box 266, Folder 10)
  - Graduate School of Business, September, October, November (Box 266, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School of Business, December, January, February (Box 266, Folder 12)
  - Graduate School of Business, March, April, May (Box 266, Folder 13)
  - Graduate School of Business, June, July, August (Box 266, Folder 14)
  - Graphic Art (Box 266, Folder 15)
  - Haq (Box 267, Folder 1)
  - Har (Box 267, Folder 2)
  - He (Box 267, Folder 3)
  - Health, School of - Men (Box 267, Folder 4)
  - Health, School of - Women (Box 267, Folder 5)
  - History (Box 267, Folder 6)
  - Ho (Box 267, Folder 7)
  - Herbert Hoover (Box 267, Folder 8)
  - Hoover Library, September, October, November (Box 267, Folder 9)
  - Hoover Library, December, January, February (Box 267, Folder 10)
  - Hoover Library, March, April, May (Box 267, Folder 11)
  - Hoover Library, June, July, August (Box 267, Folder 12)
  - Hoover Library - Pan American Division, September, October, November, December (Box 268, Folder 1)
  - Hoover Library - Pan American Division, January, February, March, April (Box 268, Folder 2)
  - Hoover Library - Pan American Division, May, June, July, August (Box 268, Folder 3)
  - Mrs. Timothy Hopkins (Box 268, Folder 4)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 268, Folder 5)
  - Humanities, School of (Box 268, Folder 6)
  - I (Box 268, Folder 7)
  - Institute of World Affairs (Box 268, Folder 8)
  - J (Box 269, Folder 1)
  - David S. Jacobson - Personal (Box 269, Folder 2)
  - Japanese (Box 269, Folder 3)
  - Jordan, Mrs. David Starr (Box 269, Folder 4)
  - Journalism (Box 269, Folder 5)
  - Junior Colleges (Box 269, Folder 6)
  - Ka (Box 269, Folder 7)
  - Kl (Box 269, Folder 8)
  - La (Box 269, Folder 9)
  - Law School (Box 269, Folder 10)
  - Legislation (Box 269, Folder 11)
  - Letters, School of (Box 269, Folder 12)
  - Li (Box 269, Folder 13)
  - Library, March - August (Box 269, Folder 14)
  - Ma (Box 270, Folder 1)
  - Mc (Box 270, Folder 2)
  - Manspeaker, Almon F. (Box 270, Folder 3)
  - Mathematics (Box 270, Folder 4)
  - Me (Box 270, Folder 5)
  - American Medical Association (Box 270, Folder 6)
  - Herzstein Lecture Fund (Box 270, Folder 7)
  - Lane Medical Lectures (Box 270, Folder 8)
  - Medical School, September (Box 270, Folder 9)
  - Medical School, October (Box 270, Folder 10)
  - Medical School, November (Box 270, Folder 11)
  - Medical School, December (Box 270, Folder 12)
  - Medical School, January (Box 270, Folder 13)
  - Medical School, February (Box 270, Folder 14)
  - Medical School, March (Box 270, Folder 15)
  - Medical School, April (Box 270, Folder 16)
  - Medical School, May (Box 270, Folder 17)
  - Medical School, June (Box 270, Folder 18)
  - Medical School, July (Box 270, Folder 19)
  - Medical School, August (Box 270, Folder 20)
  - Medical School - Auxiliary to Stanford Clinics (Box 271, Folder 1)
  - Memorial Church (Box 271, Folder 2)
  - Men's Council (Box 271, Folder 3)
  - Mi (Box 271, Folder 4)
  - Mo (Box 271, Folder 5)
  - Museum (Box 271, Folder 6)
  - Music (Box 271, Folder 7)
  - Music, Friends of (Box 271, Folder 8)
  - N (Box 271, Folder 9)
  - National, September - February (Box 271, Folder 10)
  - National, March - August (Box 271, Folder 11)
  - Natural History Museum (Box 271, Folder 12)
  - Nursing (Box 271, Folder 13)
  - Nutrition and Home Economics (Box 271, Folder 14)
  - O (Box 271, Folder 15)
  - Pa (Box 271, Folder 16)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 271, Folder 17)
  - Parents, Letters to (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - Passes (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - Patents (Box 272, Folder 3)
  - Pensions (Box 272, Folder 4)
  - Philosophy (Box 272, Folder 5)
  - Physical Science, School of (Box 272, Folder 6)
  - Physics (Box 272, Folder 7)
  - Physiology (Box 272, Folder 8)
  - Pi (Box 272, Folder 9)
  - Political Science (Box 272, Folder 10)
  - President's Office (Box 272, Folder 11)
  - President's Report (Box 272, Folder 12)
  - Psychology (Box 272, Folder 13)
  - Publicity (Box 272, Folder 14)
  - Q (Box 272, Folder 15)
  - Quad (Box 272, Folder 16)
  - Questionnaires (Box 272, Folder 17)
  - Ra (Box 273, Folder 1)
  - Radio (Box 273, Folder 2)
  - Recommendations, Letters of (Box 273, Folder 3)
  - (Regional Research Unit) National Resources Planning Board (Box 273, Folder 4)
  - Registrar, September - February (Box 273, Folder 5)
  - Registrar, March - August (Box 273, Folder 6)
  - Requisitions - Travel Fund (Box 273, Folder 7)
  - Requisitions - Travel Fund: Pending (Box 273, Folder 8)
  - Ro (Box 273, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 273, Folder 10)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 273, Folder 11)
  - Sa (Box 274, Folder 1)
  - San Francisco (Box 274, Folder 2)
  - Sc (Box 274, Folder 3)
  - Se (Box 274, Folder 4)
  - Slavic Languages (Box 274, Folder 5)
  - Sm (Box 274, Folder 6)
  - Social Sciences, School of (Box 274, Folder 7)
  - Social Science Research Council (Box 274, Folder 8)
  - Sororities (Box 274, Folder 9)
  - English - Speech and Drama (Box 274, Folder 10)
  - Exceptional Students, Committee on (Box 274, Folder 11)
  - St (Box 274, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Associates, September, October, November (Box 274, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Associates, December, January, February (Box 274, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Associates, March, April, May (Box 274, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Associates, June, July, August (Box 275, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 275, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Fiftieth Anniversary (Box 275, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Fund (Box 275, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Future (Box 275, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Illustrated Review (Box 275, Folder 6)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 275, Folder 7)
  - Statistics (Box 275, Folder 8)
  - Student Hospital Fund (Box 275, Folder 9)
  - Su (Box 275, Folder 10)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 275, Folder 11)
  - T (Box 276, Folder 1)
  - Trustees (Box 276, Folder 2)
  - Tuition (Box 276, Folder 3)
  - U (Box 276, Folder 4)
  - Unique (Box 276, Folder 5)
  - United States, September to February (Box 276, Folder 6)
  - United States, March to August (Box 276, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Army (Box 276, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Navy (Box 276, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Questionnaire (Box 276, Folder 10)
  - V (Box 276, Folder 11)
  - Wa (Box 276, Folder 12)
  - Wh (Box 276, Folder 13)
  - Wi (Box 277, Folder 1)
  - Wo (Box 277, Folder 2)
  - Women's Council (Box 277, Folder 3)
  - XYZ (Box 277, Folder 4)
- 1942-1943, Series 27
  - A (Box 277, Folder 5)
  - Academic and Alumni Secretary (Box 277, Folder 6)
  - Acknowledgements - Congratulatory letters (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - American, September - August (Box 277, Folder 7)
  - American Council on Education (Box 280, Folder 12)
  - Anatomy (Box 277, Folder 8)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 277, Folder 9)
  - Assistants (1), 1942 - 43 (Box 277, Folder 10)
  - Assistants (2), undated (Box 277, Folder 11)
  - Associated Students (Box 278, Folder 1)
  - Association of American Colleges (Box 278, Folder 2)
  - Ba (Box 278, Folder 3)
  - Bacteriology (Box 278, Folder 4)
  - Be (Box 278, Folder 5)
  - Bequests (Box 278, Folder 6)
  - Bi (Box 278, Folder 7)
  - Big Game Tickets (Box 278, Folder 8)
  - Biology, School of (Box 278, Folder 9)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 278, Folder 10)
  - Br (Box 278, Folder 11)
  - Bu (Box 278, Folder 12)
  - Ca (Box 278, Folder 13)
  - California Board of Education (Box 278, Folder 14)
  - California, University of (Box 278, Folder 15)
  - Carnegie Corporation (Box 279, Folder 1)
  - Carnegie Corporation - General (Box 278, Folder 19)
  - Carnegie Corporation (1) - History of Earlier Grants (Box 278, Folder 16)
  - Carnegie Corporation (2) (Box 278, Folder 17)
  - Carnegie Corporation (3) (Box 278, Folder 18)
  - Carnegie Endowment - International Peace (Box 279, Folder 3)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 279, Folder 2)
  - Carnegie Institute of Washington (Box 279, Folder 4)
  - Ch (Box 279, Folder 5)
  - Chaparral (Box 279, Folder 6)
  - Chemistry (Box 279, Folder 7)
  - Civil Aeronautics Authority (Box 279, Folder 8)
  - Classics (Box 279, Folder 9)
  - Co (Box 279, Folder 10)
  - Commencement (Box 279, Folder 11)
  - Commonwealth Fund (Box 279, Folder 12)
  - Composition of Boards of Trustees (Box 295, Folder 7)
  - Congratulations, Stanford Presidency (Trustee Congratulations) - [see also Box 297] (Box 295, Folder 5)
  - Conventions (Box 279, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (Box 282, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Dr. Wilbur) - Military Government Schools: War Department Material, November 1942 - July 1943 (Box 293, Folder 9)
  - Da (Box 279, Folder 14)
  - Dean of Men (Box 279, Folder 15)
  - Dean of Women (Box 279, Folder 16)
  - Defense (Box 279, Folder 18)
  - Defense - Modified and New Courses in National Emergency (Box 280, Folder 2)
  - Defense - S.U. Civilian Defense Council (Box 279, Folder 19)
  - Defense - Teen Age Draft Bill (Box 280, Folder 3)
  - Defense - War Council (Box 280, Folder 1)
  - Deferment - Selective Service (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - Degrees (Box 279, Folder 17)
  - Do (Box 280, Folder 6)
  - Dormitories (Box 280, Folder 7)
  - Duke Pacific Institute Proposal (Box 280, Folder 10)
  - E (Box 280, Folder 8)
  - Economics (Box 280, Folder 9)
  - Education - 1943-44 Work Loads Study (Box 281, Folder 5)
  - Education - 9th Service Command (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Education re: Army Teaching (?) (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - Education, School of, September to February (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Education, School of, March, April, May (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - Education, School of, June, July, August (Box 281, Folder 3)
  - Electron Microscope (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - Engineering, Civil (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - Engineering, Electrical (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Engineering, Guggenheim Laboratory (Box 282, Folder 7)
  - Engineering, Mechanical (Box 282, Folder 8)
  - Engineering, Military Science and Tactics (Box 282, Folder 9)
  - Engineering, Mining (Box 282, Folder 10)
  - Engineering, School of (Box 282, Folder 4)
  - Engineering, Science and Management War Training: Literature (1) (Box 282, Folder 2)
  - Engineering, Science and Management War Training: Literature (2) (Box 282, Folder 3)
  - English (Box 283, Folder 1)
  - English - Dramatists' Alliance (Box 283, Folder 2)
  - English - Speech & Drama (Box 291, Folder 15)
  - Exceptional Students, Committee on (Box 283, Folder 3)
  - Fa (Box 283, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Reserve Commissions - R.O.'s Pool (Box 293, Folder 8)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 283, Folder 5)
  - Financial Vice President, September, October, November (Box 283, Folder 6)
  - Financial Vice President, December, January, February (Box 283, Folder 7)
  - Financial Vice President, March, April, May (Box 283, Folder 8)
  - Financial Vice President, June, July, August (Box 283, Folder 9)
  - Fo (Box 283, Folder 10)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 284, Folder 1)
  - Fraternities (Box 284, Folder 2)
  - Ga (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - Gas and Car Pooling (Box 284, Folder 4)
  - General education Board (Box 284, Folder 5)
  - Geology (Box 284, Folder 6)
  - Germanic Languages (Box 284, Folder 7)
  - Gi (Box 284, Folder 8)
  - Gr (Box 284, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School of Business, September, October, November (Box 284, Folder 10)
  - Graduate School of Business, December, January, February (Box 284, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School of Business, March, April, May (Box 284, Folder 12)
  - Graduate School of Business, June, July, August (Box 284, Folder 13)
  - Graphic Art (Box 284, Folder 14)
  - Hanna / Davis (1) (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - Hanna / Davis (2) (Box 281, Folder 8)
  - Haq (Box 284, Folder 16)
  - Har (Box 284, Folder 15)
  - He (Box 284, Folder 17)
  - Health, School of - Women (Box 285, Folder 3)
  - Health, School of (1), September - February (Box 285, Folder 1)
  - Health, School of (2), March - August (Box 285, Folder 2)
  - Herbert Hoover (Box 285, Folder 5)
  - Herstein Lecture Fund (Box 288, Folder 13)
  - History (Box 285, Folder 4)
  - Hoover Library, September, October, November (Box 285, Folder 6)
  - Hoover Library, December, January, February (Box 285, Folder 7)
  - Hoover Library, March, April, May 1943 (Box 285, Folder 8)
  - Hoover Library, June, July, August 1943 (Box 285, Folder 9)
  - Hoover Library, March - August 1943 (Box 285, Folder 10)
  - Hoover Library - Pan-American Division, September - December 1942 (Box 286, Folder 1)
  - Hoover Library - Pan-American Division, January - April 1943 (Box 286, Folder 2)
  - Hoover Library - Pan-American Division, May - August 1943 (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 286, Folder 4)
  - Houses for sale on campus (Box 286, Folder 6)
  - Housing and Feeding (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - Humanities, School of (Box 286, Folder 9)
  - Humanities, School of - Rockefeller Report (Box 286, Folder 8)
  - I (Box 287, Folder 1)
  - Institute of World Affairs (Box 287, Folder 2)
  - J (Box 287, Folder 3)
  - Japanese (Box 287, Folder 4)
  - Jordan, Mrs. David Starr (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - Journalism (Box 287, Folder 6)
  - Ka (Box 287, Folder 7)
  - Kl (Box 287, Folder 8)
  - La (Box 287, Folder 9)
  - Law School (Box 287, Folder 10)
  - Li (Box 287, Folder 11)
  - Library, September - February (Box 287, Folder 12)
  - Ma (Box 287, Folder 14)
  - Manspeaker, Almon F. (Box 287, Folder 15)
  - Mathematics (Box 287, Folder 16)
  - Mc (Box 287, Folder 13)
  - Me (Box 287, Folder 17)
  - Medical School, September (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - Medical School, October (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Medical School, November (Box 288, Folder 3)
  - Medical School, December (Box 288, Folder 4)
  - Medical School, January (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Medical School, February (Box 288, Folder 6)
  - Medical School, March (Box 288, Folder 7)
  - Medical School, April (Box 288, Folder 8)
  - Medical School, May (Box 288, Folder 9)
  - Medical School, June (Box 288, Folder 10)
  - Medical School, July (Box 288, Folder 11)
  - Medical School, August (Box 288, Folder 12)
  - Medical Society, California State (Box 288, Folder 14)
  - Memorial Church (Box 288, Folder 15)
  - Men's Council (Box 288, Folder 16)
  - Mi (Box 288, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous - Selective Service (Box 280, Folder 11)
  - Mo (Box 288, Folder 18)
  - Mrs. Timothy Hopkins (Box 286, Folder 5)
  - Mumford, Pacific Islands Research (Box 289, Folder 1)
  - Museum (Box 289, Folder 2)
  - Music (Box 289, Folder 3)
  - Music, Friends of (Box 289, Folder 4)
  - N (Box 289, Folder 5)
  - National, September - February (Box 289, Folder 6)
  - National, March - August (Box 289, Folder 7)
  - Natural History Museum (Box 289, Folder 8)
  - Naval Flight Preparatory School (Box 294, Folder 7)
  - Navy Training Schools - information requested by Bureau of Naval Personnel (Box 293, Folder 10)
  - Nursing (Box 289, Folder 9)
  - Nutrition and Home Economics (Box 289, Folder 10)
  - O (Box 289, Folder 11)
  - O.S.R.D. (Box 289, Folder 12)
  - Pa (Box 289, Folder 13)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 289, Folder 14)
  - Parents, Letters to (Box 290, Folder 1)
  - Passes (Box 290, Folder 2)
  - Patents (Box 290, Folder 3)
  - Pensions (Box 290, Folder 4)
  - Philosophy (Box 290, Folder 5)
  - Physical Sciences, School of (Box 290, Folder 6)
  - Physics (Box 290, Folder 7)
  - Physiology (Box 290, Folder 8)
  - Pi (Box 290, Folder 9)
  - Planning and Development Committee (Gifts) (Box 293, Folder 4)
  - Political Science (Box 290, Folder 10)
  - President's Office (Box 290, Folder 11)
  - President's Report (Box 290, Folder 12)
  - Psychology (Box 290, Folder 13)
  - Public Relations (Box 290, Folder 14)
  - Publicity (Box 290, Folder 15)
  - Quad (Box 290, Folder 16)
  - Questionnaires (Box 290, Folder 17)
  - Ra (Box 290, Folder 18)
  - Radio (Box 290, Folder 19)
  - Recommendation, Letters of (Box 290, Folder 20)
  - Registrar, September - February 1942-43 (Box 290, Folder 21)